Tanner Stoker

Web Developer

Phone 7023531021

E-mail tannerstoker@gmail.com

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/tanner-

stoker-78133a17

WWW tannerstoker.com

WWW https://github.com/Tanner016

Solution-driven professional excelling in highly collaborative work environments, finding solutions to challenges, and focused on customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web sites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and more. Experience building products for desktop, phone, and mobile app users, along with meeting the highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, usability, and speed. Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and building web applications aligned to customer's services. Translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs, third-party integrations, and databases.

Skills

HTML5	Excellent
CSS	Good
JavaScript	Good
React	Good
Redux	Good
Node.JS	Good
Bootstrap	Very Good
Flexbox	Good
Git/GutHub	Very Good
Website optimization	Very Good
Marketing	Excellent

Work History

2017-07 - Current

Web Developer

Elite Web Growth, Henderson, NV

- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement. Worked with countless clients to improve their website look, performance, and overall results.
- Implemented Google and Facebook Campaigns and SEO for various types of websites to bring clients new customers and visitors to site.
- Converted mock-ups by clients into HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON, resulting in over 30 complete website and landing page creations.
- Used programming capabilities in PHP, SQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed to fulfill clients needs.
- Implemented website and integrated solutions into business operations to improve the overall fluidity of website and business management.
- Determined coding requirements for site creation, including e-commerce capability and specialized scripts, then worked with clients to produce the most cost efficient website possible.

2015-02 - Current

Web Developer

Stoker Enterprises LLC, Henderson, NV

- Built and managed 3 complete online eCommerce stores, over 30 landing pages, and an Amazon store.
- Utilized efficient and creative SEO and website practices to produce \$30,000 in year 1 revenue with a sub \$500 yearly marketing budget.
- Slashed overall costs to maintain yearly profit every year of company existence.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement by utilizing customer feedback to produce the best results.
- Developed page layouts and navigation tools that met or exceeded user expectations and allowed for nearly full automation of all website activities and sales.

Education

2018-10 - 2019-08

Certification of Completion: Web Development

Zero To Mastery Complete Web Development

2017-01 - 2019-12

Bachelor of Arts: Economics

Utah State University - Logan, UT

2014-01 - 2016-12

Economics

University of Nevada - Las Vegas - Las Vegas, NV